

ABOUT

After graduating from University, I went to the United States for a couple of months to work. In my time in the US, I worked there as a line cook and photographer. After returning to Turkey, I worked in the fields of Digital Marketing and E-commerce for almost a year. During this time, I became enthusiastic about software development. I enrolled in a course at Neos Software and also did my internship there. While I was taking that course and later, I supported my learning process with Udemy courses and by building my own projects. Nowadays, I am working on Node.js, using Express.js, MongoDB, and Mongoose for back-end development, along with more advanced React for front-end development.

SOCIALS / CONTACT



ardsen.github.io



github.com/ardsen



linkedin.com/in/ardsen/



+90 507 123 6938



as.ardasen@gmail.com



@ardsen - @ardsenn



Ankara, Turkey

LANGUAGES

Turkish English



Arda Şen

Web Developer

EDUCATION

Corum Anatolian High School (2010-2014)

Hacettepe University (2016-2022)

-International Relations (English)

Neos Software Academy (05.08.2023 - 01.03.2024)

-Software Specialization Course

EXPERIENCE

Guitar Instructor (2019-2022)

During my university years, I provided guitar lessons to a limited number of students to earn extra income.

• Work and Travel Exchange Visitor Program (2022)

Dave & Buster's - Myrtle Beach, SC

Line Cook (June 13, 2022 - September 16, 2022)

Hollywood Pictures, Myrtle Beach, SC

Photographer (August 2, 2022 - October 10, 2022)

Digital Marketing / E-commerce Specialist (2022 - 2023)

Aydın Psikoloji Yayınları

• Internship (01/04/2024 - 15/05/2024)

Neos Software Academy

SKILLS / INTERESTS

- HTML
- CSS
- Javascript
- React
- Node.js
- MongoDB
- Python
- Django
- SQL

- Wordpress
- Adobe Premiere Pro
- Adobe Photoshop
- FL Studio / Audacity
- MS Office
- Gutar / Mus
- Video Games
- Books
- Museums